[theme music playing]
-We need to meet.
-All right. I'll be there.
[Emilia] You follow that Camia woman.
I'll follow Ivy Aguas.
[Camia] As much as I want
to stop worrying, Lily, I can't.
Especially since you've reached
the point of having
a relationship with the enemy.
How long will this go on, Lily?
Until marriage?
[Ivy] I won't let it get that far.
You have to watch out.
I'm worried that Emilia
might get desperate,
and you don't know what she's capable of.
We used to be helpless
against the cruel Ardientes,
but now we can hold our own against them.
It's from Jaguar.
That money is very important
because we will use it for the elections.
[Arnaldo] Don't worry,
I'll guard it with all my life.
[Emilia] I have no patience
for Ivy, Aunt Claire.
I have to resort back to my old tricks.
[Claire] Like what you did to Camia Cruz?
Are you ready for your new assignment?
-Yes, ma'am.
-Good.
-Ivy, I'm going to break in.
-[Ivy] Diego, don't.
We have to make sure what's inside first.
We might find some important evidence.
[Arnaldo] Who were you talking to?
[Ivy] You're doubting me too?
I'm sorry if I upset you.
I think the only way
we can fix this is for you
to have dinner with my mom.
Ivy agreed to have dinner with you.
Are you excited for our dinner?
-Of course.
-I shall see you.
[Ivy] I'm very excited, Emilia.
Emilia and I are having dinner
at the Viento.
[Diego] Ivy, be careful.
[Ivy] Where's Emilia?
I said, where is Emilia?
[grunts]
[goon] All right! Strip her clothes!
[goons holler]
[goon] Take them off!
[goons laughing, hollering]
[goon] Strip her naked!
[goons whooping, laughing]
[goons laughing, speaking indistinctly]
[goon] Strip her naked!
[goons whooping and hollering]
[young Lily] Mister, please don't. Please.
Mister!
Please let me go! Mom!
[goons hollering]
[goons speaking indistinctly]
[suspenseful music playing]
[action music playing]
[goon exclaims]
[Diego] Hey!
[grunts]
[goon grunts and groans]
[action music continues playing]
[goon] Get up!
[Diego grunts]
[Ivy] Diego!
[Ivy grunts]
Diego!
[goons grunting]
[grunts]
This is odd.
Our gambling associates have
never been late to our meetings.
I find it strange too.
Maybe they're just busy?
[scoffs] Busy? Whenever I call a meeting,
they always drop whatever they're doing.
I'm telling you, Arnaldo,
something's not right.
-[Segovia] Congressman.
-Oh, Segovia.
Where are our partners?
They all left. Jaguar took over
most of our gambling operations.
[Julio] Son of a--
[exhales sharply]
[exasperated sigh]
[indistinct chatter]
[goon] It's Mr. Jaguar! Mr. Jaguar!
[goons] Mr. Jaguar!
[goon] Mr. Jaguar!
Listen up!
In order to show his appreciation,
the Jaguar prepared a surprise for you.
[tense music playing]
Who ordered you to attack me?
Who ordered you to do this?!
[gunshots]
Answer me. Who do you work for?
You don't want to answer me?
Even if you don't tell me
who's behind this,
-I know you work for Emilia!
-[gunshots]
You're all scum!
If you try to follow me,
I will kill you. You understand?
Ivy, let's go.
-Tell Emilia…
-Let's go.
I'm not afraid of her!
-Tell her that!
-[gunshots]
[sighs] Looks like I'm going
to have a restful sleep.
Wow. Finally. I so deserve
a good night's sleep.
Beauty rest.
Good. I hope you don't get nightmares.
Aunt Claire…
Why are you raining on my parade?
Emilia, you've done a number of
unspeakable things in the past,
and I never said anything about it.
But to have another woman raped…
That's unacceptable.
Auntie, when it comes to that woman,
I don't care about morals.
And that's what she wants anyway, right?
For men to lust after her.
That's why I'm giving it to her.
Besides, you know, every time
I see that woman,
you know, she's like Camia.
They love it when men go crazy over them.
That's the reason my husband fell for her.
It's a good thing
my sex appeal's stronger than
Camia's, that's why Raul
and I are still together.
Honestly, the problem with these women
is they only rely on their looks.
If they rely on their looks,
what about you?
Seriously, Auntie? Are we okay?
Do we have a problem or an issue?
You better give me the correct
answer, or you'll be sorry.
What were you saying again?
[ominous music playing]
Nothing.
Great.
Let's go, Ivy! Wear this.
Ivy, hold tight.
[melancholic music playing]
[Arnaldo] I think we should take
that Jaguar down, Grandpa.
That is what I really plan to do.
I can't wait to see
that Jaguar cower like a kitten.
[Julio laughs]
-Excuse me, Papa.
-Yes, Raul?
Uh… [grunts]
I'm going to put this here.
Someone wants you to have it.
Don't touch it, Arnaldo.
Jaguar sent that. I can feel it.
Papa, if you don't mind me asking…
What is it about that Jaguar?
Are you afraid of him or something?
I'm not afraid of anything, Raul.
Now, just to humor you…
Let's do it, let's open it!
Let's see what Jaguar sent us this time.
Oh…
-What is that? Dirt?
-[Julio laughs]
It's supposed to be symbolic, Arnaldo.
It's a symbol of…
death.
[Julio] Silly Jaguar!
What is he trying to say?
If he was here, I'd dump that at his feet.
Just to show him that his scare
tactics aren't working at all.
You know what this is, Arnaldo?
This was done by a child!
This is a childish display of bravado!
This Jaguar guy should ask
his mother for some tips
on how to fight like a man.
Well, anyway… Let's go!
[groans] I've had my share of
bad comedy for the night.
By the way…
-Good night, Jaguar!
-[Arnaldo chuckles]
-Excuse me, Raul. Good night.
-Okay, Papa.
What should I do with this?
Uh…
You can either return it to Jaguar
or look for him
and stuff him in that bag.
[Julio laughs]
Hey.
I thought you were having
dinner with Ivy, Mom?
That's what I thought too!
I kept calling your girlfriend--
Sorry, I mean your fiancée,
but she hasn't been answering my calls.
You know what? That woman's
nothing but a pretty face.
She has no class at all!
Okay, enough with the insults, Mom.
First of all, I don't believe you.
It's either something bad happened to her,
or worse, you're behind all this.
Wow!
Mamita, tell me.
Did Mom have something to do with this?
No comment.
[Julio scoffs]
My grandson is asking a question.
Where is Ivy Aguas?
-Papa!
-I am not asking you.
[sighs]
I'm asking you though, Claire.
[tense music playing]
[Julio] Well?
Are we just going to stand around,
or will you keep the ball rolling?
[somber music playing]
Ivy…
Follow me, Ivy.
Let's spend the night here.
It's not safe right now.
[phone ringing]
Hello, Ivy?
Who are you?
-Ivy?!
-Where's Emilia?
Julio, I may not be an Ardiente by blood,
but I know my alliances.
And I won't jeopardize that!
-[Julio] Okay.
-[Claire] That being said…
No, Emilia had nothing to do with this.
See, I told you!
We shouldn't even be talking
about this to begin with!
I had nothing to do with this!
Aunt Claire just said so!
I'm really offended! For all we know,
your girlfriend-slash-fiancée
went to see another man.
Or maybe, she's hiding something.
Auntie, let's go.
[sighs] Good grief.
How does that rhyme go? Liar, liar…
Pants on fire.
-[chuckles] That's your mom!
-[exhales heavily]
[instrumental theme music playing]
We'll make the Ardientes pay.
[crying]
I'm so sick of it.
I want to give up.
But if I do…
I'll get killed.
And I can't let the Ardientes
get away with the things they do.
So, no matter how hard it is for me…
even though it hurts so much,
I have to endure
because I have to keep fighting.
I know that someday
it will all make sense.
I won't let another child
or family experience
what I had to go through.
I won't let that happen.
I won't let what happened
to Nanny Carlotta
happen to anyone else.
I won't let it.
[instrumental theme music playing]
And when you finally get justice…
what will you do?
I hope I do get it.
When I do, I don't know.
I don't know.
That's it? You're just
going to frown at me?
The least you can do is thank me.
-For what?
-For keeping your secrets!
Exhibit A. Hiring someone to spy on Diego.
Exhibit B. What you did to Ivy.
How much do you want
for keeping those secrets?
[scoffs]
You can't bribe me
with something you don't have.
[crutches clacking]
Bravo. Bravo.
Bravo, Claire.
Maybe we can offer you something
that we Ardientes do have.
And that is… the protection
that we can provide you.
Well, it's just an offer. Think about it.
If you turn your back on us,
you're courting danger.
[Julio] Hmm?
-I'm not betraying you.
-Good, very good.
Claire.
Keep your secrets to yourself.
And Emilia, my dear daughter,
I applaud you.
I applaud your initiative.
Finally, you learned something from me.
Now, you're truly starting
to think like a true Ardiente.
Placing a mole in Diego's camp.
Stroke of brilliance.
And the attack on Miss Aguas?
Right target, good intention.
Bad execution.
-But, Papa?
-[Julio] Emilia.
Don't treat Miss Aguas
like Raul's mistresses
that you can easily get rid of.
If Arnaldo finds out about what you did…
[tut-tuts]
Your son won't be able to forgive you.
[tense music playing]
A little advice to both of you, ladies.
Carry on.
But do tread lightly, ladies.
Is there another appointment
you haven't told me about?
Remember that I'm paying you
to tell me any kind of
information about Miss Aguas.
So, please, give me something!
But there's nothing else, Mayor.
Nothing?!
-I'm sorry.
-Nothing?! You're useless!
What do I pay you for?!
When we finally get justice…
I'll build a house here.
I saved up for this,
because when I was a kid…
I dreamed of having my own property.
And I told myself…
that I'd live here with…
If…
if she wants to…
I'd live here with Lily.
I know she'd love it here
because it's far from the Ardientes.
["Hindi Kita Iiwan" playing]
Ivy, I want you to be happy.
I want you to be free from this burden.
I want you to be happy, Ivy.
And I hope you'll let me be part of it.
["Hindi Kita Iiwan" playing]
Ivy.
You know how much I love you, right?
["Hindi Kita Iiwan" playing]
[line ringing]
Come on. Come on. Come on.
-[line ringing]
-[screams]
Answer the phone!
[line ringing]
-[line ringing]
-Ivy--
[screams]
[romantic music playing]
Diego, I love you.
I might find it hard to accept
most of your decisions.
[Diego] And I'm always worried about you.
But there's one thing I'm sure of…
You have a forgiving heart…
and you remain to be a good person
despite all the bad things
that happened to you.
Ivy, I promise you…
that I'll be here for you until the end.
I will do everything I can
to end your suffering.
I love you so much.
["Hindi Kita Iiwan" playing]
I had Aunt Camia double-check everything.
I'm prepared for my speech too.
What about our program?
It's all set. The band said
they'll perform for free too.
The sound system provider…
allowed us to pay them later.
But let's make sure
to settle our balance on time.
All right, I'll find a way.
I'm actually here at my property.
I'm planning on selling this
to get more funds.
[Marlon] Okay, good.
I'm sure a lot of people
would be interested in that.
We can get more funds through that.
Wait, where is that?
Do you want me to go there?
No, don't. It's all right, Batch.
You always keep…
secrets from me.
Wait. I think our future
governor got a girl.
[Marlon laughs]
So, tell me, who's the lucky woman?
Don't tell me you forgot about Lily.
You're nuts. Anyway, I have to go.
[chuckles] All right. Okay.
Diego.
Thank you again…
for what you did.
Um…
I need to go home.
After that, I need to return
to the Ardiente's mansion
because I can't just ignore
what Emilia did to me.
Ivy, be careful.
Uh…
I didn't mean to eavesdrop…
but are you really going
to sell this property?
Diego, I know this is important to you.
If it's okay with you,
I'd like to buy this property.
So, when the time comes
that you need the land back,
I'll give it.
Ivy, I can't accept your offer.
Thanks for your concern…
but I want to win because of my hard work.
But I promise that
I'll get this land back someday.
Shall we go?
What do you think about having
a motorcade before the filing?
That's a good idea, Governor. We'll do it.
Great, Jun.
-Execute the plan.
-Let's take note of that.
Let's execute that. Get it ready, okay?
Arnaldo? Do you know
that I have better things to do
than to watch you lose your head
like a lovesick puppy?
[sighs]
Your staff is here to give you
a briefing for tomorrow.
As what Ma'am Emilia learned
from her intel,
the opposition is ready.
We won't back down.
We'll double our efforts.
The cultural dancers
have already rehearsed.
Aren't cultural dancers
a bit old-fashioned?
We also have sexy dancers
to attract people.
We'll be there first thing in the morning,
to make them seem like the copycats.
Right.
Before we plan this, may I look
for my future first lady?
Um…
Guys, can you just leave us
-for a while?
-Okay, Governor.
-We'll just discuss things.
-Okay.
-[groans]
-Thank you.
[clears throat]
-[Loring] Is this it?
-[Marlon] It's nice. Thank you.
You can go now.
-[Camia] Thank you!
-[Nimfa] Oh, please do eat.
-[Diego] Thanks, Nimfa.
-[Loring] Take this, Diego.
This is our donation.
It's from Pandoy and the other farmers.
Nanny, you shouldn't have.
Thanks, but you shouldn't have pitched in.
Diego, what do you mean we didn't need to?
Of course, we need
to make sure you'll win!
We're ready to sacrifice anything.
Thanks, Nanny.
[Loring and Marlon chuckling]
[man] Diego, we're thankful
for your compassion.
Especially when you fought
to protect our land
from being stolen by the Ardientes.
That's why we'll do everything
to help you win, right?
[everyone agrees]
-Thank you so much!
-Right. Right.
-That's right.
-Thank you.
[Loring] Yeah.
We assure you that once Diego
has liquidated his property,
and has been taken in by a party,
we're going to give you your money back.
But, Sir Marlon, which party
will Diego be running with?
I hope it's a huge party, so the
Ardientes won't stand a chance!
That's right.
Nimfa, what about your father, Fernan?
Is he joining the rally tomorrow?
I haven't seen him around. Where is he?
-[Pandoy] Yeah, that's right.
-[man] Yeah.
-[Marlon] He's gone?
-[Loring] Yeah?
Um, he's in Manila right now,
taking care of some business.
He didn't want to leave,
because he wants to help
with Diego's campaign.
But it's okay because we'll get
back at those corrupt
and heartless Ardientes!
[loudly] I can't understand
why they keep winning!
That's why we should unite
for Diego's cause!
[everyone agrees]
[indistinct chatter]
[Nimfa] I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry. I'm so sorry.
When I talk about the Ardientes,
I get so worked up.
[everyone laughs]
[Pandoy] Same here!
[Loring] You're just like your father!
[Marlon] I guess so, right?
Arnaldo, you're the governor,
not that woman. She's useless!
I won't file for that
damn candidacy until I find Ivy.
Okay? That's final.
No. It is not final, Arnaldo.
Look at you. What's happening
to you? What's wrong?
You know, that woman's
trying to brainwash you.
Now, you're even going
against your own mother!
You keep taking her side over mine.
Your own flesh and blood.
How can you do this, Arnaldo?!
You're even jeopardizing
your own political career
for that woman!
And I'm not gonna allow this
to happen, Arnaldo.
I'm not!
[scoffs] Thing is, Ivy isn't the problem.
You are!
You can't accept that I'm marrying her.
I don't get it! What's your problem?
You know why?
Because I despise that woman.
You know, I'm like a mad dog
dying to shred her into pieces
every time I see her!
Until all that's left of her
are her rotting skin and bones.
And I just happen to be your mother,
and I'll do everything in my power
to call off your wedding to that woman!
Even if it takes having her killed!
How dare you!
I'm on the verge of forgetting
that you're my mother and
slapping your beautiful face!
The moment something happens
to Ivy, you will answer to me!
Remember that.
You're insane. You're sick!
Excuse me. There's a letter for Mr…
-Diego Torillo.
-Batch…
go get some snacks.
[man] Diego, someone's looking for you!
-Hey, Diego.
-[man] You have mail.
[Loring] What?
What is it?
-There's a letter for you.
-It's a letter.
-Delivery.
-I'm Diego.
Kindly sign here, sir.
Here you go. Thank you.
Thank you, sir.
-[Loring] Oh.
-Take care.
[indistinct chatter]
What's in it?
-Hey, that's a check.
-A check?
That's a check?
-What is this?
-Nanny…
[Pandoy] Whoa!
[both blabbering]
[man] That's a huge amount.
-[Marlon] That's big.
-[Camia] Who sent this?
Miss Camia, it's from an anonymous donor.
This will be a great help to our campaign,
and we can build
our headquarters with this.
-Exactly!
-Right?
[indistinct chatter]
[Loring] What should we do?
We better keep it somewhere safe.
Nanny, hold on.
We can't just accept this money.
Who would donate this much money?
Batch, candidates always
receive anonymous donations.
These donors try to help
the candidates they want to win.
The candidates they believe in.
And these donors are big-time businessmen.
[Loring] My goodness.
I'm sure this person has an ax
to grind with the Ardientes.
-[laughter]
-[indistinct chatter]
[Pandoy] That's right!
[Marlon] We're on the same side.
Diego, take it.
That's for your campaign
and for our whole cause!
Right, everyone?
-[everyone agrees]
-[indistinct chatter]
[singing and humming]
Emilia!
[suspenseful music playing]
I-- Ivy…
[stammers] What are you doing here?
What am I doing here?
I'm here to show you that
I am very much alive and well.
Of course, you are, you should be.
[grunts]
-[smashes piano]
-[Emilia coughing]
You bitch! Stop playing dumb
because I know you're the one
who hired those men to rape me!
I'm here to tell you
that you can never take me down.
[smashes piano]
What? Cat got your tongue?
What?
What is it, Emilia? Go on.
You were saying? What do you want to say?
Why are you blaming me?
Why not?!
I'm not playing games with you!
[Emilia grunts]
Remember this, Emilia.
Remember this. Remember this!
That's the last time you'll ever
get a chance to finish me off.
Because next time,
I won't hesitate to kill you.
I'll kill you! I will kill you! You bitch!
[tense music playing]
FOR THE NEW ARDIENTE
Batch, this looks great! Right, Uncle?
And these too.
We'll make more of those
and give them to your supporters.
-Diego, add this to the fund.
-Thank you, Auntie.
[Pandoy] Wow.
[Loring] I'm getting worried about this.
Do we really have to place
the funds here in the house?
Here, I made some coffee and snacks.
Thank you, Nimfa.
-Thanks.
-[Loring] Thanks.
[Diego] Thank you.
Nanny, you're the one I trust the most.
Besides, we'd all feel safer
if all the campaign materials
were kept here.
All right. Okay. Here then.
I better put this away.
[Pandoy] All right. We better put it away.
[Loring] Yeah. That's right.
We better take these too
and post them all over town.
We better go too. Batch.
Let's go, Kris. Let's go.
-Let's go.
-Bye, Miss. Camia.
-Take care.
-Let's go. Let's go.
-See you later, Batch.
-I'll come back for it later.
-All right.
-[Pandoy] Loring!
-[Loring] Yes?
-[Pandoy] Come with us.
[Pandoy] We're going to
distribute these to the voters.
-Let's go, Mrs. Loring.
-Okay.
-Take care, guys.
-[Loring] We will. Thanks.
Aunt Camia.
I need to tell you something.
Have you spoken to Ivy?
[smashes piano]
-You want that, huh?!
-[Emilia groaning]
-Maybe it's time for you to die.
-Ivy? Mom!
Ivy! Let go! Let go! Enough! Enough!
-What the hell is wrong with you two?
-What happened?
Do you know what your mother did?! Huh?!
She sent her men to try and rape me!
And I'm sure she planned to kill me too!
Is it true?
Answer me. Is it true?
Well, Emilia?
Say something.
Your son asked you a question!
[Camia] What?!
Emilia sent people to rape my daughter?
Diego. I have to talk to her right now.
I have to make sure
that my daughter is okay.
Auntie, wait. Ivy's all right.
Don't worry.
Were you the one who saved her?
My poor daughter!
When will her suffering end?
Diego, I want to see her.
I want to hug my daughter.
And I want to face Emilia…
so that I can beat her senseless.
Aunt Camia, calm down.
I know this isn't easy for you.
But if you let your anger
get the best of you,
it might ruin Ivy's plans.
There's a right time to be angry.
That's what I learned from Ivy.
Right now, we should prepare for
our meeting with the Ardientes.
[Julio] Excuse me, ladies.
Emilia…
Why do you think Miss Aguas
is accusing you of that?
Papa, why would I do that?!
Why would I even do that?
This woman is delusional!
She's sick in the head. A major cuckoo!
-Ivy, Ivy, Ivy.
-Delusional? Are you sure?
You're the only one
who could've done that to me.
-Do you have any proof?
-You want proof?
Who made the reservation
at the restaurant?
Wasn't it you? It was under your name.
But where were you?
I was trying to call you,
but you weren't picking up.
-How's that?!
-I know it was you.
You're the only one
who could have done that to me.
You know what, Ivy?
Since you're so good at making up stories,
you should go see a doctor
because you're sick in the head!
-Major cuckoo!
-I'm not sick in the head!
-You're crazy!
-And I'm not making things up!
You're such a good actress.
Why don't you see a doctor, instead?
Because no mother in her
right mind would ever send men
to rape her future daughter-in-law.
You're crazy.
Be thankful I'm friends with the chief,
or you'd all be in jail right now!
Incompetent fools! You're all pathetic!
How could all of you
let one woman get away?!
[goon] She wasn't alone, ma'am.
Diego was there to help her.
I don't care! You're useless! [grunts]
Nobody talks to anyone
about this! Is that clear?!
-Yes, ma'am.
-Leave, now!
[phone ringing]
[ominous music playing]
[clears throat]
-Hello, Nimfa.
-Hello, ma'am.
Make sure that Diego and
his group don't find out
I sent my men to rape Ivy, okay?
Uh…
Of course, Ma'am Emilia.
Oh, by the way…
I know where Camia's funds are hidden.
And it came from an anonymous donor.
It seems like Diego
and his group are rich now.
That's rich enough for you? [chuckles]
That's nothing compared
to what the Ardientes have.
Okay, Ma'am Emilia…
So, you take care of Ivy,
while I take care of Camia.
I can feel it too.
I'll catch those two together.
Okay, just make sure you keep
your promise before I keep mine.
[tense music playing]
She will not get away with this!
I'm telling you…
Tell me what those men
looked like, and I swear,
I'll kill them all!
I'll kill my mother too.
I swear, I will do everything for you.
I will avenge you…
I will avenge you, and I'll make
sure everyone suffers.
I'll make sure everyone suffers.
Every single one of them.
Leave me, Mr. Mayor.
"Mr. Mayor"? I am your fiancé.
I'm… I'm not going anywhere!
Okay? I'm not going anywhere.
I'm staying here.
I can take care of myself.
Well, I used to have Nanny
Carlotta to take care of me,
but now, she's gone.
So, whoever killed her…
should know that it feels like
I've died too.
[sighs]
Ivy…
Carlotta is gone, but I am here, okay?
I'm your family now,
so I'm not going anywhere.
Okay?
I'm not going anywhere. I'm here for you.
[Diego] Ivy, I want you to be happy.
I want you to be free from this burden.
I want you to be happy, Ivy.
And I hope you'll let me be part of it.
Ivy, you know how much I love you, right?
[Ivy] Diego, I love you.
I'm not going anywhere.
I'm staying right here.
I'll keep fighting until
we can be together, Ivy.
[screaming] Who did this to you?!
Tell me!
A-A-T. Arnaldo Ardiente-Torillo.
What do you have to do
with Nanny Carlotta's death?
[indistinct chatter]
[Emilia] Do you know
what your mother did?!
She sent her men to try and rape me!
And I'm sure she planned to kill me too!
[tense music playing]
Get away from me.
Hon, what's wrong?
What's wrong?
-Get away from me.
-What's wrong?! Hey!
-Get away, Arnaldo!
-What's with you?!
-Get away!
-[screams] Is it my fault?!
Tell me!
I don't get you.
I'm trying my best to understand you.
Okay, fine. Given… Given you're in shock.
Fine. I will go the extra mile
to understand you.
Fine.
Get some rest.
Rest for tonight, so you can come with me
when I file for candidacy.
I love you. I love you, Ivy.
I love you so much.
Arnaldo, please.
Go home.
[dramatic music playing]
[tense music playing]
[supporters] Diego! Diego! Diego! Diego!
[Camia] You are the queen of hired killers
and hired rapists in this place!
Why would you even think
that Ivy would be supporting us
if she knew that I was the one
who tried to have her raped?
Ivy, come on. Speak up.
[screaming]
[Ivy] What happened? Oh, my.
Congressman, could this be an inside job?
[Emilia] Sabotage.
I want to cripple them all.
[Nimfa] You'll be surprised, ma'am.
I can say that it'll be a blast.
[theme music playing]